Good morning.
I finally did the horizontal tensioning.
I'm looking forward to it.
Because we always use it in Fils.
But there's a microwave!
Great!
Good morning, everyone.
Is everyone here?
Has anyone arrived yet?
No? Yes, number one! Welcome, everybody! Is everyone here? Anybody here yet?
Are we there yet?
Yes!
Oh, this way.
Look, a microwave oven.
One big room, one person.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no,
The dressing rooms are too big. A very big dressing room.
It's a very big dressing room.
Here you go.
Wow, it's huge!
You can sleep.
Here's the backstage area for this show.
It's too big!
All right.
I'll do my best.
I'm going to wait for everyone.
Where shall we sit?
Oh, my God, it's the day of the show, and I'm so excited.
I took a lot of pictures in front of the arena.
I took a lot of pictures in front of the arena, but there wasn't a lot of people there yet.
Have you seen this one?
Love and Youth, this, this, this.
The panel, I don't think they knew us at all.
He was staring at us.
And then, when we were in the transparent side split, there were a lot of staff members there.
There were a lot of staff members there.
And they were stuffing flyers.
So...
Wow, so many people are doing this for us.
I thought, "Wow, so many people are doing this for us.
And I'm so happy.
I'm so happy!
Good morning.
No, no, no.
Here he comes.
I thought you might be the first one today.
I came quite early.
I was bored when I came.
I could see it.
I saw Hiyori's big panel of love and youth on the front,
Hiyori was taking a picture of it,
Oh, that's Hiyori, I took a picture of her.
I'm so embarrassed. I didn't notice it at all.
And then you went into the convenience store, right?
I went into the convenience store.
You had it, didn't you? Before?
Well, I had been going into the Daily Yamazaki since before I took it.
I bought rice crackers.
So I thought I'd follow you, but you came out too early, so I didn't really get to the convenience store.
Really? The storage is amazing. I thought I was going to follow him, but he came out too fast and I didn't catch up with him at the convenience store. Oh, that's true.
The hangar is amazing.
Why?
It's amazing.
I heard it's like this.
Really?
Okay.
I'm so happy.
It's going up.
It's up. I don't know what to do.
I'm the only one who can see them.
We're always in different rooms.
Oh, I see.
Yeah, you know, I always use it for festivals and stuff, but...
I've been using it, but...
Weren't we each given our own room?
No, I don't know.
That's a little bit sad.
It's lonely. There's a microwave.
You can heat up your lunch.
See, it's already warmed up. I miss it. There's a microwave oven. See, it heats up the bento.
See, it's already warmed up.
Good morning. Please.
Please do.
Oh, it's bento.
Duk-duk-duk-duk.
Now, let's go to our dressing room.
Oh, here. What's that?
We've been waiting for you. It's not big.
It's big.
Wow, you can lie down on the sofa.
Maybe we can all lie down.
It's great. It's great.
That's great.
Wow!
Wow, I'm so happy.
I'm so happy.
Yeah.
I was on my way here, too.
I also thought about it while I was coming, trying to think about the number to stir up the crowd one more time.
Thank you for coming to Yokohama Aline in the first place,
I thought, "Well, that's all right," and thought about it again.
Then I started to cry again.
The other day, at rehearsal, I couldn't get that phrase out.
Good morning.
It's hot.
It's a little bit bad.
I'm outside right now.
I acted like a fan.
And I went inside the fence.
There was a fence, and there was a panel inside.
I went inside the fence.
I don't know if it's okay.
They didn't get mad at me.
It's not good.
I only dream about it.
I'm so nervous.
I can't sleep.
I don't know what to do.
We only use them at festivals.
I'm sure we can get one for each of us.
We have room.
But I don't want to do that.
I don't know where it is.
It's so loud.
Good morning, ma'am.
Are you sure you're doing well?
I'm doing great!
There you go again.
It's a little fugly, so I came out.
It's really cool.
I knew you'd have a lot of luggage anyway, so I was able to carry it, but not this much.
I thought I'd have to get off at the remote anyway, so I could carry it.
I saw it, I saw it, I saw it, I saw it like a panel.
I'm scared! All I could think about last night was what if I fall off the lifter?
I'm so scared.
What's it like?
Here it comes! The day has finally come!
I finally started to feel it yesterday and the day before, and I'm getting a little nervous.
I'm so nervous.
But I'm not looking at the stage.
I'm kind of looking forward to it.
I'm going to get on here as soon as possible. I'm almost there.
I got this photo, so one is in the fridge, and one is in the gutter. Cold drinks.
Yay. Let's go for it.
Yay, let's go for it!
Today, tomorrow and the day after tomorrow only.
Yokoyuri spec phone in a case.
Cute stickers
I'll do my best!
I tried to put Yokoyu in a suitcase, but only a big suitcase would fit.
I brought Yokoyu with me.
I'm going to decorate my room!
I'm so excited!
Even the yuzu salt looks delicious!
Yuzu salt and yuzu salt are also delicious!
This is matte coffee.
I put a lot of matte coffee in here.
Oh, my God! You came?
We got a big guy here, a really big guy. .... This is it, right? This is it. This is a comment from a bamboo.
Yokoyuri-kun!
Nice to meet you, Yokoyuri-kun.
It's nice to meet you.
Please do me a favor.
I have a girl named Sabrin in my house, so I hope we can be friends.
YouTube.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Cute.
You're pushing Kaname, aren't you?
There was a pause.
No, it wasn't.
It's the same blue.
But it's not a canary press.
It's so calm.
I froze.
Stop it!
It's like you haven't gotten used to the groove yet.
It's got the word "woge" on it.
I'm a little lost.
Her butt is pudgy.
He's cute.
I'll bring your lunch later.
Oh, my God, I don't know if I can do this.
It's a tour!
It's a stage tour!
There are usually so many performers, but I really wonder if it's going to be okay. It's a tour. It's a stage tour.
There are usually so many performers here.
Today, I'm using the best backstage at the lip.
I'm using the best dressing room.
Oh, yeah!
The best microwave oven! It's everyone's favorite microwave oven.
The best, the dream, the day I spend with you.
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh!
What, eh, awesome!
I'll think of more when I get there. Oh, man! It's so cute! Look! Isn't it amazing? It's floating. How did you do that? Look at that.
It's like an illumination, these lights.
Warm colors.
Bright. Cute.
Look at them. They're not ordinary lights.
Can we all see it?
Already?
Are they here?
There you are! Oh, my God! Is that candy?
Oh, my gosh! He's so cute!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
It's so cute.
Oh, man, it's so cute! Oh, man, that's so cute. Oh, it's cute!
Oh, man!
Are we really going to do our own show?
I'm kind of looking forward to it.
Open it over here.
Ew, ew.
Wow!
No, I can see LEDs.
It's too cool.
Come on, everyone.
Yes!
This is the actual position.
Where you said it was a little cramped...
I'm having it fixed.
Thank you very much.
I want you to take one home.
Where would you like to put it?
I want one.
Let's go home.
Oh, I'm scared. I'm scared.
It's around 6, so be careful.
Oh, I'm scared. Calm down.
Oh no!
I'm going to follow my nose for a bit.
Oh, this one.
Oh, I think I can do it.
Let's go!
Let's go
What's that? It's a staff member.
There's a mirror ball.
It's a slope, isn't it?
Oh my God, it's too cute!
Yuri's love gave it to me.
It's so cute!
Oh, no!
This is the dance floor!
So cute!
It's even cuter from afar
It looks like a strawberry.
So cute!
Amazing.
Here's another one.
And here we go...
A moving stage,
The moving stage is separated from the stage.
Oh, our own show? What?
A live performance by Tokisen?
Really?
Really, boss?
I'm not sure.
Are you there?
Whose show is it?
Mr. Tokise? What's up?
I'm good. It was a free show.
Maybe I should get on with it.
Let's get on with it for two days.
You know, when we usually do the side split, there's a flower aisle right here.
Isn't it fresh to have it here?
It's fresh to have the audience here.
It's totally different from the way it was made.
The set is so cute!
Thank you very much.
I don't know where to say it.
I don't know where to say this.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, to the hearts of all the staff, where should I turn to say it? Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
To the hearts of the staff,
Rock on!
We are the Super Scimeci Advertising Department.
Please give us your best regards. I am the prettiest of the prettiest
Ooh-oh-oh-oh.
You're the only one born in the spot.
Arrieta Slide Kick Chong
I don't know why
I sure do when I laugh
It's like the world is shining
I can turn my umbrella around and take it easy 'cause otherwise I wouldn't be able to walk
I'm sure somewhere someone's crying, somewhere I'll get wet again, won't I get cold?
Wetting my body, I wonder if it's not cold
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying, just a little bit of my feelings
I want to share it with you
I still don't know what's in front of me
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turns color
On the canvas of my broken heart, I'll paint the shards of the future
I can tell you now the reason for my tears
Whenever you're lost, just remember
I'll try to smile even when it rains
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are sparkling
It's as if my heart is in a sunny mood
I'll play the rainbow piano with the sound of the rainbow
Goodbye Goodbye to Yesterday's Me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny sky, let my tears dry
I'll wear a rainbow dress Bye, you